Go!
Kickoff!
You got this!
We have one strength
and one strength only.
An advantage in numbers!
SHIN TENMA RYOHEI JUZO
KITO
If we keep passing to whoever's open...
There it is!
O-Ogami!
Huh?
He was on the opposite side!
He's fast!
Let's start things off
with a little hello, shall we?
He's shooting already?
Huh?
No way!
He knocked the goal over!
Boss, be careful!
Don't blow your cover with a kick!
Like I care.
I'll worry about excuses...
after I wipe that smug look off his face!
Out of bounds!
Kick-in for the home ec team!
Was that for real?
That was actually kinda crazy!
That was way beyond "kinda"!
Tenma's...
kicking power is totally pro-level, but...
Not bad.
Well, I can kick things at least.
I've never lost a game of
Kick the Can for distance.
HOW ABOUT A "THANK YOU"?
SATURDAY, MAY 16th
Ooh, look at Oga go!
Did he forget that whole "living quietly
and staying under the radar" thing?
Wow, Ogami's incredible!
That was amazing!
Wait, could this actually
turn into a real match?
Huh? Wait...
Oh, I'll take the kick-in.
Thanks.
What's wrong, Shin?
Kohazame?
D-Dude, where's your pacifier?
I-I don't... see it.
Huh? Sea lion?
Wait, was it when you tried
to block that shot?
Los... Blancos.
Without his pacifier, this guy turns
into a useless bundle of stage fright.
What?
Honestly, before anything else...
I was wondering why he was
always sucking on that thing.
Right?
Ah...
Must've knocked it loose
when it grazed him.
Do you have a spare?
Um, he says there's one
in his bag in the classroom!
I'll go get it!
I'll go, too!
Thank you!
Fine.
Just stand here for now.
Maybe you'll at least be in their way.
Our advantage is gone!
Now it's just a normal 2v2!
Hey!
Can we get this game going again already?
Noren, he wants you to be
his lap pillow and pat his head?
That's his dream?
That's what he said.
Everything about him is over the top!
This guy...
There it is!
Good, it's in a case!
I was worried
it might just be loose in there!
Okay! Let's hurry back!
Although, that pacifier seems to
come with a lot of baggage.
Huh?
Did he tell you about it?
Yeah.
I asked why he was
sucking on that it.
That was really direct!
I mean, it'd be weirder not to ask.
I guess because it calms me down.
But if you ask me why...
my mother, who isn't around anymore,
gave me a pacifier with a kind smile.
That hazy memory is the only one I have.
Maybe it has something to do with that.
He might have a pretty heavy past.
Why not do the lap pillow?
I don't think a lap pillow has
anything to do with that.
Okay, what's happening with the game?
What the heck happened?
Oh! You're back!
Shin's been on fire,
making one god-tier save after another...
against Tenma's killer shots!
That's not "on fire"!
He's getting massacred!
Intercept!
This is bad! Noren, get this to him now!
Huh?
If he takes any more of that,
he's gonna die!
Wait, die? But how am I supposed to...
Throw it!
You're probably the best athlete here!
Oh, for crying out loud! What is this?
Shin! New pacifier incoming!
ANPAN
- Huh?
- What the...
Sorry, but things won't go
the way they did before.
I'm quite confident in my footwork, too.
He stopped it!
Is he the same guy as five seconds ago?
- Shin!
All right, let's go!
The real match starts now!
Somehow, you're the only one
who's going into battle mode.
- Go!
- You can do it!
That feint's totally basic,
but he's just plain fast!
Dammit!
Changing speed in a split second?
That's it!
The pacifier freak
isn't the only reason Tenma can't score!
This guy looks like a total amateur,
but what the hell is he really?
Out of bounds!
Aw, so close!
That was incredible! Are you getting
better and better as we go?
Well, sure, I do wanna beat Tenma.
But that aside...
Playing sports again after so long
is a ton of fun.
Yeah! Wait, after how long?
That sounded too much
like an adult, Boss.
There's still tension, but it's nice
that nobody's trying to kill me.
Trial and error and
responding to the challenges...
is kind of exciting.
Hey, Tenma...
PEDESTRIAN TRAFFIC ONLY
Hm?
The way you keep singling out Ogami...
Is it because, deep down,
you're looking for a rival?
Huh?
You were born with that athletic physique,
but you never slack off, either.
You're superior in every sport you play.
But you're alone at the top. Maybe that's why...
you're itching for someone
who can face you as an equal.
Nah, not at all.
Huh?
I like totally destroying people.
If I could win 100-0, I would.
Wow, I was totally wrong!
I'm doing three sports because
I love all three too much to pick one.
And that whole "alone at the top"
thing you mentioned?
That's actually what I want to be.
Every sport has its legends, right?
And no matter how good
today's players are...
they always get compared to those guys.
That pisses me off.
But what if I leave behind legends
in three different sports?
And not some soft,
watered-down kind of "unique."
I'm gonna be so one of a kind,
nobody can ever deny it.
He's so far gone, it's almost refreshing.
If we weren't childhood friends,
I'd stop hanging out with him.
So, yeah, I'm not really looking
for a rival or anything.
But I do have frustrations
from being all alone up here.
Huh?
What the...
All right!
Yeah! Nice!
This is getting fun!
I said I like destroying people,
but it's not like
I'm into kicking corpses, you know.
It's just so hard to find...
a toy I can play with at full strength
without breaking it.
All righty!
Time to get serious!
He's not bluffing.
I don't think I've ever heard someone say
a cliché like that with a straight face.
People get this wrong all the time,
but when Tenma doesn't go all out...
it's not exactly him playing around.
All he ever thinks about
is improving himself.
And to do that, he never actually
takes it easy on anyone.
But if he overwhelms them too hard
and they give up, that's a problem for him.
So, depending on the opponent,
he limits the kinds of plays he uses,
or the area he's allowed to move in.
Basically, it's a self-improvement
challenge run.
You should be proud.
Tenma almost never takes
his shackles off in any sport.
He's only dribbling!
But it's like trying to stop a boulder!
Hah!
Wha...
Wha... So fast!
Tenma scores!
That's our superman!
No question about it!
A jaw-dropping three-man breakaway!
And that's the end of the first half!
Tenma's team heads into halftime
with a one-point lead!
That was insane.
I have to admit, even though we're
on Oga's side, that got us hyped, too!
Getting the crowd this fired up
with one play?
That's pure superstar energy!
Even three-on-one isn't enough.
What are they supposed to do?
Would you let me take them by myself?
Huh?
Do you have some kind of plan?
Nope.
What?
Well, I'm the one who picked this fight
in the first place.
But never mind that.
Anyway, just let me do this. Please.
- Go!
- The second half is underway!
Does the home ec team have
any way to turn this around?
Wait!
Man-on-man?
You seriously think you can beat me?
I'm taking point number two!
I can't shake him!
Why not?
What the hell is going on?
Even if he's got freakish athletic ability,
how can he keep up?
Is it just me...
or does Ogami look like he's...
having fun?
It's not like I've got some chance
of winning, or some big plan.
It's just...
back when I was really a kid,
I hated losing.
No matter how stupid the contest was,
I'd take it seriously.
But the more I grew up...
the less I got fired up about anything.
At work, all that matters
is producing reliable results.
But the more accomplishments
and years I stacked up,
somehow, life just kept
getting duller and duller.
I just remembered how I felt back then.
That feeling of playing my hardest and
going head-to-head is damn great!
Thanks!
Because of you,
I'm having a blast right now!
What are you, an old man?
Crap!
But yeah, I agree.
This is what a match oughta be!
And in the end...
I'm gonna win!
This is one hell of a back-and-forth!
- Go!
- Neither one's giving an inch!
Just a minute ago,
he could barely keep up!
There's no way Tenma's losing
in raw physical ability!
Is he predicting Tenma's moves? No...
He's getting a feel for his rhythm.
Whether it's an official sport
or an underworld fight to the death,
one-on-one, the fundamentals are the same.
You identify the exact moment
your opponent will move and match them.
It's a straight-up kicking clash!
I swear I'm gonna win!
They're even on sheer willpower?
No, we are not even!
I'm still holding one hell
of a grudge, you little punk!
Don't look down on the home ec club.
Take a good, hard look
at yourself and do better!
Don't do it because it's convenient
for you or whatever.
Do it out of gratitude for the person
who made food for you!
When someone makes you rice balls...
how about giving them a thank you!
It's in! Goal!
It can't be!
He scored!
The home ec team comes out of nowhere
with the equalizer!
- Yeah!
- We did it!
All right!
Man, what happened to you?
You actually lost a clash!
Come on! We're getting
that point back!
Hey...
I give up.
I can't keep going after that.
I forfeit.
This is my loss.
Huh?
What?
What did he just say? He's giving up?
That's it?
Give up? Why now?
You're really fine after that?
It's a shock for me, too.
I hurt myself in that clash just now.
If I keep pushing like that, it'll affect
the sports I'm serious about.
I'm not looking down
on this game or anything.
I only take stupid risks for the
sports I'm actually betting my future on.
I hate to admin it, but I can't continue.
Huh?
We won?
Game set!
For real?
Tenma lost?
Boo!
Yeah, well, with an ending like that,
I can't blame 'em.
Fair enough.
I'll take the booing.
More importantly, Ryohei...
can I lean on you?
Walking's harder than I thought.
What? Dude, you're huge and heavy!
I know.
Hey...
Is there tape in the first-aid kit?
Well... yeah.
Give me your foot.
This isn't exactly my specialty,
but it'll be better than nothing.
Probably.
The home ec club's president...
Shiraishi. Chisato Shiraishi.
Now the sock, too.
Why?
I still haven't apologized
like I promised.
And besides, I'm the enemy.
What are you talking about?
Jeez, do battle maniacs only see
the world as enemies or allies?
Now, it's true that your comments
got under my skin.
In fact, I was ready to personally...
But... that's a separate matter.
When someone's in trouble,
you help them.
That's all there is to it.
There. Done.
That's the kind of club we are.
That said, the fact that you have a clear
dream you're willing to put first...
even if it means
getting booed in the moment...
That's worthy of respect.
I borrowed some crutches!
Need these?
Everyone in the home ec club...
I'm not saying this because I promised to,
but because I truly mean it.
I'm sorry for making fun of you!
The rice balls you brought were delicious!
Thank you very much!
For better or worse, he is honest.
Hey!
Huh?
Ryo's with you, too?
Yeah, I had a book I forgot to give Ogami.
He should be here soon.
Hey...
Oh, Ogami—
Ogami?
What happened to you?
Well, after all that, people
started recruiting me like crazy.
I mean, you were pretty amazing out there.
Like, not normal amazing.
That was a fluke! You know,
some kind of freak adrenaline rush!
What are you gonna do?
I told you that you'd end up
drawing a ton of attention!
What do I do?
Hello!
Huh?
Why?
Tenma Tendo?
Hey, don't look at me
like I'm some kind of ghost.
Don't tell me you're here
to join the home ec club, too!
No, I'm not.
Also, why are you always
sucking on that thing?
There's something I have to do.
Huh?
Well, more like something I want to say.
To you, Chisato.
I've fallen for you.
Please go out with me.
Huh?
What?
I'm the best when it comes to sports...
but outside of that,
I didn't understand anything.
You made me realize that, Chisato...
and now...
I want to be with you forever!
Wait... Huh?
Hold on!
This sort of thing is...
I'm not used to it, or rather... why?
I'm bad at this, but more like...
how brutally direct is your approach to life?
Master?
What the hell do you think you're doing...
hitting on my precious big sister
out of nowhere?
I'll freaking kill you!
Wait! Are you one of those
loves-his-big-sister-way-too-much guys?
I don't care if you're a Unicorn
or popcorn, I'll grind you into meat!
Calm down, Master!
Tenma! Just get outside for now!
Huh?
Just do it!
Master's already
in Thunderclap and Flash stance!
Man, give me a break!
What the hell were you thinking,
making a joke like that?
It wasn't a joke. I'm serious.
First Shin and now this guy...
What is with these people?
Ever since that match, every sports club
in the school has been chasing after me,
I can't focus on my school life!
I just want to study quietly
without standing out!
Without standing out?
Quietly?
You want to study?
Right, you're the kind of guy
who wants to stand out, wants to excel...
and doesn't want to study.
That's impossible.
You already stand out.
I don't know what you're hiding,
but it's all gonna come out eventually.
You're the least normal person here.
An amateur doesn't beat me in a clash
by fluke or sheer guts alone.
I've never seen anyone like you
at the top of any sport.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Even without all this,
it might only be a matter of time.
But even so...
I wouldn't trade this peaceful
school life for anything.
It's irreplaceable.
So...
I want to keep it going
for as long as I possibly can.
After that, maybe as an apology to me...
he pulled a little string for my sake.
TENMA TENDO, VIRAL SUPER MIDDLE SCHOOLER,
BEGINS A LONG-TERM RECUPERATION
Word got leaked that
Tenma Tendo was injured...
LONG-TERM RECUPERATION?
HIS INJURY MIGHT BE THE CAUSE?
...and the sports magazines and news sites
were suddenly all over it.
TENMA TENDO BEGINS
LONG-TERM RECUPERATION
YOUNG PRODIGY TENMA TENDO
BATTLING AN INJURY SINCE SPRING
Of course, that wasn't actually true.
The story he wanted to spread was...
"The only reason
Juzo Ogami won"
"was because Tenma was in nearly
the worst condition of his life."
That took my reputation back down a peg,
relatively speaking.
The sports club recruiting frenzy...
and all the noise around me
gradually died down.
Incidentally...
When I asked him if that meant he'd be
sitting out all the summer tournaments...
I'll just say I got healed up and
make a miracle comeback!
So, there you go.
Worked out great, huh, Boss?
Man, that was close.
I managed to cover it up somehow.
Right?